<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<language>
    <phrase name="hero_title">Welcome to </phrase>
    <phrase name="hero_subtitle">your gateway to efficient and dynamic web development powered by PHP!</phrase>
    <phrase name="hero_button">Get Started</phrase>
    <!-- ABOUT -->
    <phrase name="about_title">About Us</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_subtitle">Start your journey with light-framework today, and let's shape the future of web development together!</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_sub">Dynamic web development powered by PHP!</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_tab1">At light-framework, we understand the vital role that a robust and flexible light-framework plays in crafting exceptional web experiences. Whether you're a seasoned developer or just starting your coding journey, our PHP-based light-framework provides the tools and structure you need to build powerful, scalable, and feature-rich web applications.</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_tab2">Explore the possibilities of streamlined development with our carefully designed architecture, which empowers you to focus on creating innovative solutions rather than getting bogged down by repetitive tasks. Take advantage of our comprehensive documentation, tutorials, and community support to accelerate your learning and stay ahead in the ever-evolving world of web development.</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_tab3">Whether you're building a small business website, an e-commerce platform, or a cutting-edge web application, light-framework is here to elevate your development experience. Embrace the power of PHP and unleash your creativity with a light-framework that's designed to simplify and enhance the way you build the web.</phrase>
    <phrase name="about_description">Unlock the full potential of web development with Joudev. From streamlined workflows to powerful features, Joudev is your key to building dynamic and scalable web applications. Try it today or elevate your website with our professional services. Embrace the future of web development</phrase>
    <!-- features -->
    <phrase name="features_title">Empower Your Web Development Journey with light-framework: Try It Today or Elevate Your Website Now!</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_title_tab1">Try the light-framework</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_title_tab2">Elevate Your Website</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_title_tab3">Ready to Transform? Order Your Website Now!</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_decs_tab1">Unleash the potential of PHP-driven development. Dive into a world of efficiency, flexibility, and innovation. Experience the ease of crafting powerful web applications with our user-friendly light-framework.</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_desc_tab2">Transform your online presence with the light-framework advantage. From seamless navigation to dynamic features, give your website the edge it deserves. Elevate user experience, performance, and functionality effortlessly.</phrase>
    <phrase name="features_desc_tab3"> Take the leap and kickstart your digital transformation. Our expert developers are ready to turn your vision into reality. Order your website now for a bespoke, high-performance online presence.</phrase>
    <!-- Services -->
    <phrase name="sertives_title">Our Services</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_subtitle">Our Comprehensive Services: Elevate Your Digital Presence</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab1">Mailbox</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab1">Streamline communication with secure and efficient mailbox solutions. Stay connected effortlessly.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab2">Analysis</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab2">Harness the power of data with insightful analysis. Make informed decisions and optimize your strategy for success.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab3">Design Excellence</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab3">Transform your vision into reality with our creative design solutions. Captivate your audience with visually stunning aesthetics.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab4">SEO</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab4">Boost your online visibility and reach your target audience effectively. Our SEO experts optimize your content for maximum impact.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab5">Dedicated Support</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab5">Experience unparalleled customer support. Our team is here to address your concerns and ensure a smooth journey.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab6">Deadline Management</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab6">Stay on track with our deadline management services. Deliver projects on time, every time.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab7">Strategic Planning</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab7">Craft a roadmap for success with our strategic planning services. Align your goals and pave the way for sustainable growth.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab8">Domains and Hosting</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab8">Secure your online presence with reliable domain registration and hosting services. Experience seamless performance and 24/7 uptime.</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_title_tab9">Mobile App (PWA)</phrase>
    <phrase name="sertives_desc_tab9">Extend your reach with a compact and powerful mobile app. Stay connected with your audience on the go, offering them a seamless and engaging experience.</phrase>
    <!-- Project -->
    <phrase name="projects_title">Our Projects</phrase>
    <phrase name="projects_subtitle">Non hic nulla eum consequatur maxime ut vero memo vero totam officiis pariatur eos dolorum sed fug dolorem est possimus esse quae repudiandae. Dolorem id enim officiis sunt deserunt esse soluta consequatur quaerat</phrase>
    <!-- Contact -->
    <phrase name="contact_title">Contact Us</phrase>
    <phrase name="contact_subtitle">Let's discuss how our tailored solutions can propel your business forward. From concept to execution, we're here to turn your vision into a digital reality.</phrase>
    <phrase name="contact_message">Get in Touch and Ignite Your Digital Transformation!</phrase>
    <!-- Q&A -->
    <phrase name="qanda_title">Frequently Asked</phrase>
    <phrase name="qanda_title_strong">Questions</phrase>
    <phrase name="qanda_subtitle">Unlocking Clarity on Your Digital Journey</phrase>
    <!-- Blog -->
    <phrase name="blog_title">Blog</phrase>
    <phrase name="blog_subtitle">Recent posts form our Blog</phrase>
</language>
